tiobe.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy Statement | TIOBE - The Software Quality Company

TIOBE Software is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the www.tiobe.com site. It does not apply to other offline TIOBE sites, products or services. By accessing the site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

## Collecting Your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, email address, company name, phone number, and region. The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used for the operation and improvement of the Site.

## Use of Your Personal Information

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.

TIOBE may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TIOBE or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TIOBE and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of TIOBE employees or agents, users of TIOBE products or services, or members of the public.

## Control of Your Personal Information

Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of TIOBE Software without your permission.

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to TIOBE in the context of other, separately operated, TIOBE products or services.

## Cookies

We use cookies to analyse our traffic and to show ads. By using our website, you agree to our use of cookies.

## Changes to This Privacy Statement

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

TIOBE welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that TIOBE has not adhered to this privacy statement or if for any reason you wish to view or delete data and personal information TIOBE has stored about you to support its service-processes, please contact us by e-mail at info@tiobe.com, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

Send mail to [webmaster@tiobe.com](mailto:webmaster@tiobe.com) with questions or comments about this web site.
